{
    "id": "bb00cdc4d55344d49def6cf9ec6dd1d6",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy worked hard ………………………….. he did not succeed.",
            "description": "However is not a conjunction it cannot connect two clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "but",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he is very popular, he cannot be called a great writer.",
            "description": "We use though to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Despite",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. his kind nature, he never had many friends.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is followed by a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Though",
                "Despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… his homework, he went out to play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Finished",
                "Having finished",
                "Being finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. poor, they suffered great hardship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "Been",
                "Having been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We must eat ………………………… we cannot live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He bought the estate …………………………. belonged to his uncle.",
            "description": "The relative pronoun which refers to things. We use it to connect two clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "it",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the inflation, the standard of living has increased.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a pity ………………………….. we should have to suffer this humiliation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. you search his pockets, you will find the watch.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The young bride went near the bed ……………………………. the old man could bless her.",
            "description": "So that indicates purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was so tall …………………………. they had to make a special coffin for him.",
            "description": "So...that.. expresses cause and effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "and",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}